The good
the girl. Or.
The the.
Good the girl.
The
girl.
The girl.
The
crispy but don't shine tight you don't
shine I'll shut up I want to lose two
percent this week shouting.
I want to listen got
a lotta
a lot of you guys been united need to fight
to get that in the on the back and up
she got to chat with them I think the wife
to say I'm not going to talk oh yes you
are not going to get rid of me but you'll
still be Reno Tahoe still might like the
package and I'm not going to have any bullies
hanging around what do you mean Will
you come to me I'd love to do my bit in
town just one county does the asshole my
spine good idea Donna the if you were to
cosign nothing because you need eight
years ago to go on the screen now you wept
when you took you out of the coast if it
was not to spend your time
going around with boys you got
a lot to. The.
The.
What.
The and. Just.
The and. The are.
Valid.
Issue now some are. This
woman was never. She was
strangled with
a long. Back to the body piece. Of iron
which if you found the body such as you
didn't get I don't ask the court to
strike but he says he did but he didn't
contradict the evidence and that is just
a moment if you don't mind. I don't miss
much OK Well we were best came down today
and just to got try and get piece of tape
we saw this young man running away it
just said I'm going to get killed you and
you were running away wasn't yelling
That's right nonsense you go to
bed at the top I'm never just
a little. Your way running away you know
you want to spend tested I saw the bodies
on the top the piston actually came down
I'm going to show she was either dead or
any unconscious You see I didn't see the
belt so I don't have to get help that I
could ask you to
especially as when you get
a few minutes is when there's
only been Davis you.
Know
the
same.
Well let's start with religion now is this
yours or is it one hundred time I do it
just how do you know it isn't You've
already admitted that you've got
a raincoat don't put down God but had
a raincoat which you lost no not lost
which I had stolen while you tried to do
everything like that and get excited old
man is down there for an hour then you had
it stolen let it go at that when was it
so. You see I looked in the time when to
get into the reds when I came back it was
gone you mean it just when I think you
see in there what sort of a face was this
a common shove to call Tom's head all right
we'll let it go now did you know the
dead woman well is fairly well I knew her
name it would be unfair to suggest that
you were especially good friends Mr Kent
main was the done done and we can put down
that you were friends good friends over
don't much like where you are good enough
friends to discuss money what's the idea
we discussed money three years ago when I
told her
a storage they've been
good hard cash. Paid
. Talking of money would it be accurate
to say that you were not well off
inordinately that perfectly true would you
considering the fact that she's left you
twelve hundred pounds and well.
What happened to him Bastardo pretended
to be past our side in terms of Amalia.
That put on his head of course didn't
happen how did he down that he's.
Going back to Brown. If you could be pretty
good at this sort of thing if I learned
something about the news go that. You learned
that slapping trick in the guides to
no I don't actually writing in cards is
a tactic. You do that to detectives
is well you know I got this from
a box of criticism because
a man like funny it takes for them you don't
notice it when you had the rest of the
take session might say well this group is
all that you know you can depend on these
so they are right in the neighborhood
you've been doing to know he's all right
don't waste your sympathy on him there's
been going to the guilty no idea yet so I
didn't look like
a criminal you know look killing two young
ladies. I don't. And it is not my tribe
it will. The devil have you
part of it if you can live
a little part down but you need to know
something very much like you so why don't
you go.
It's going time for artists. Who seem to
like the brand. You'll probably go again
next time Joe back in to watch your kids.
To sample she's consequence daughter
she's got no she's not my hands.
We're in paradise I've heard proceeding
to be quite formal when at least I can
understand why the question of the nature
of the Scotland Yard Whenever with
a gypsy someone decent to represent and I
think I've got Mr Big to talk sense it's
pretty well there was no one else that I'd
really be trying to sniffing around and
if not it's my cup of coffee and get on
with it but normally I will expose you to
stand beside it being a projection with
a disgusting subtitle tried to make you
want to love it and we walk and did it and
I couldn't move which got me
the interest of the court.
Come on. To some other time has now been
caught my eye getting it's been branded.
With what is. I agree that live
on it. Must be downhearted on
a morning like this much me as one good
to see the sun doesn't it my wife was
saying only this morning Henry Don't be
so gloomy about the case she said I just
wasn't the we haven't had
a case like this for twelve
years added to be expected in
a little place in this fog mostly affiliation
orders and things like that know
a case like this is most
exciting for us all wouldn't be
a good thing to talk to. Do any actual harm
will be plenty of time in this all the
trial trial Linus repeated I did.
Now when I say. Two years well now
well it doesn't look too good does
it however we mustn't be depressed about
it now he's playing those two girls that's
all you're running away why are you running
away I wasn't you know oh well it's
very likely I mean that's going to be very
hard to explain away like the money that
poor dad creature lent fuel and it's going
to be hard to explain away two years
that it looks very like noted to me and
whether we must understand now it actually
does. He'll disappear and only now I should
be very much happy and all the match
much happier if it were not for that belt
now do you mean like the devil to divide
girls and then find the blasted cold I
swear it was told in the tongues hat last
year had to know oh well met
seventy nine we had that's quite
a good point always indeed Tom had it
a common shelter on the main Compton
road when I get my coat of the belt I be
should realize what
a colossal blunder they're making Well of
course I'll do everything I can for you
though I do wish you had been more frank
with the police about it it always pays to
be frank with the police now and are you
representing the peace by any chance mean
you know my dear fellow I am on your side.
And tell me when they say that you did
they leave you your money and yet. Two
pounds three shillings and wonder if it
would be asking too much of what I have
a trifle on account of that
matter how much I thought you had
a couple of pounds Oh thank you here's
a great pity if you hadn't
any money Council costs
a great deal you know however perhaps
you've got some friends who come to your
rescue at the last minute
your case dismissed
a great. Dear. Dearly I just mislaid my
glasses you know and I'm quite lost without.
Ask him to delay proceedings for the
little while and you shall be able to
read my notes nothing new to paste in
a day like this must mean.
Hold on
a minute the application just finished Yes
here's where we need to go into battle.
This is this and do we really want
a separation or the oh no savage I don't
want him to carry on of me said that. The
decedent will promise me to behave yourself
and your child I also may be I were of
a date with. You. As what I
should buy and you told him to
keep the peace for six months or so can
you make it eight months academy over
Christmas no. That little space.
Spelled I have to deal with well hell I
do want to talk about the things I ask
Charlotte just. Take.
Is this is the romance.
This is.
Just a potential benefit analysis
a look at it in
a. Delicious
.
Haven't you got some damage to the assumption
that the down to the man touch the
spinning the provider the
denominator right are left out on
a pole if you can't help others with deficits
to you to send you to fix the so then
a million metric you can Iran actually made
I didn't make it actually funny how to
make mistakes and when I point out it is
a limitation of the limits
of the eighty eight
an hour. Eight
S.
Sudden they can make the decision the
Internet makes your life nonexistent even
a piece of the line toward Russia. Despite
addiction All right you think of the
South Pacific to do it but that's alright
with your name address chef if you've got
a backpack you're going to be coming. To
town now because you can't stop without
that. Bank up at.
Eight.
So right on top I thought you
must have missed it wasn't
a I feel you know whenever captain this was
going to go on you know what about you
because you're right off like.
I was on young man old furball I got
a comment you are going to what it was your
top in the name of the law you can't do
that to neglect where I am at this for
the moment we've got to get to the right
away station quickly I can't go quickly
takes don't like we can't help it we're on
a job take his night job I'll be alright
myspace gone down but I have to find him.
Now they literally shit takes so long.
To get
a bit more room to talk don't
read old morning ten pages. Well
if you didn't I was not doing what you're
doing can you imagine she remember who I
am yesterday the chief constable is going
to minus two million jobs I didn't get up
to the top. Then should I tough the countryside
looking for you. So Michael this is
now this is I mean I'm just going
hoping you understand because you're so
calculated sized interested but you know
me you know we've come to the crazy you
haven't I hope this tape you actually have
to tell the police is going to lose one
thing you should still think they were
pushing the car. Thank you so you should
just as I'm doing
a little work. To
it to gather she. Turns out I'm going.
To write about this great man who will. Be
wanted by the police really get that up
so you start stop the effort to fill up
if you see that and I tell him to keep on
escaping but the business I
certainly will. All right.
Thanks. Very. Much to
an eleven. Minute. Seem to exist in
a way to turn the money to
a new way and I think. Given the state
pride of it. Comes out in
those headlines that wrote
about by just power you can shake up of
that moment of time I reckon and can ride
along in my laptop and to my Metro not
by talk right off at the back down.
Left and trying to map that road. Here
that's my idea right now is to just turn
like Long Island take
a left oh yes I said. I don't forget
it's my. Great defect road lake
about five miles thank you right.
This is me Tom said we hope you get
out because it's my car this in
a good reason for you it doesn't mean passion
that it's the best thing you can do.
Aside from your world or no I certainly
have not left I have you feel it is too
risky to me to go down head by daylight
what do you do now to be dissipated in the
desert
a million to darken the return of dried
milk to tomcat before it closes. Like
a Lebanese into the mist
if you want to talk
a little while ago I was stunned not to
give if I like about your decision how can
your joke about it don't you know what
it means of course I'd make Alaska is
probably around when I didn't from you to
know that I can laugh because and then to
be think you. Wish to do. Well
when you learn to do.
Unless you're going to go into
a bank stooping to give. A
talk that said inaction.
Just because you're pumping that's
not going to get money. No Thea no.
It didn't touch my heart it doesn't isn't
the only thing is I must have my potatoes
next you know I don't mind going to the
dentist he would Johnny want to read first
I won't Yes you were lucky I could tell
exactly what the. Big business to do could
only go nonstop in a nice
conversation I may have to have
a great start to decline. Then you're going
off and I'm on the cell phone going to
you shouldn't either of them have it it's
highly dangerous time with the teaching
here to be done speaking English
Jaimee being only shut up now that is
a myth because Come to think anyway because
I want to now Chris Christie if I don't
do disgust it's
a jolly fine way to do it because we don't
rush or have watched him well known to
you. Sergeant Joe if you were not
a bit too late to give us time. I had to
push inform on haven't they called in the
last year and it's hardly
a matter of time of course of course
my day I walked from his job to
a full ride to MIT so I had no potatoes
mash with milk so right then fast Erica It
really depends how much
money and that's often
a big factor in cases like
this people that never had
a can make sure I must be having the thing
about three feet I don't lose and this
is due to the problems in exams. If you
wash your hands between us and don't want
to done didn't manage to make you spend
their last three shillings it looks to me
as if each course not correct the crap.
That tender Christabel Oh. I'm going to
make things right Sanderson just wanted
to react with probably didn't want it was
like You've got the back yard planted on
the produce checked my God I'm going to
talk to. The president talk too much too
much with you. I want to mock you by just
lastly shooting food of course I know that
time is not kind of food softly and I
sing we'll be talking as if it has been a
good thing so you didn't take going to
a shop to get food then I'm afraid you'll
be getting hungry and then of course May
fourth and come back I'm going to
fight hunger not it's not taking
a dime. You stick to the shipping
and. Perhaps this time you.
Know music school. There might be some.
Good. Or I'll come along with.
You know what you're going to. Have
to call them that. The police
say was again diabetic I.
Finally get back the. Little Bridge I
don't need much chance to inspect village
only have come to me I shoot him in
the region check. Kiting isn't it.
Looking to the. It ended up blow
you really do think I mean this
was
a total act. I came back
to Can I did it. Two
. Hundred. Identical now.
And. Perhaps should I be
dangerous feel good I'm here.
Seriously I'm very grateful there's any
consolation to you I want you to know that
I'm innocent and. Just that I know
nothing about how to do this if I made
a dash for the school I know they're not
going to take on the shelves and put an
end to this crisis which. The minute I.
Still did not know any
better thirty four hours
a day given the free speech with. The
table.
With the past with humility like in the
night that I did not return or. I just
forgot. A lazy attempt. Now what am I
a spitting playlist
tangled up in a link to
a new hand can produce more rain put it
stolen I'm going to finally spill purity
and I should tear. Into
one. Of these and. It
doesn't go on what you consider.
Did you know Christian. Now.
And if it has been. Like to the story I
wrote and asked me to go now minutes of I
went to a party three or four times still
in the under bet see that what that
a paper coming out of the all male someones
in their pack should say Yes come on
and so I did
a good turn but never teach the supposed
leader something you know Will. Just about
this why question about my going to print.
Grab
a hold of them make nice just on the edge
but what if he bites me in the course the
duty you make to describe such good must
try to find not now want to where you
don't go out and grab
a little dogs. To
Rocky Mountain climbing shot.
Anyone I know Alan Mollohan just
no time for a family you've got
a lot to never looked.
All I saw just now when I say I'm sure I
can say now when did you know it's course
I did then I'm going to make sure I'm
she got no confidence in me Sergeant
non-eternal. Good mind to go up and have
a look myself. I
had to. Look after the seal
turns out best and form
a ring. Oh
stop. The car. To watch if you stop
if you don't stop I'll jump out.
Sounds like Thank You God Now next up Tom
said what would it matter that Bob said
Marjorie crossroads syndicalist for
two miles beyond that and into
a lot of trouble on top of your trouble to
me thank you very much what you've done
your baby is on the way she talks about it
biking is my friend she taught me how to
drive my car the chief constable come
to understand my mom's an uptight.
Told me to give me
a caution you guys could. Store
was. Going to take
a left off anyway. I'm
just not going to come to my greatness and
I'll find out what I can about the coach
I might as well to. True
none. Of. That hide
behind. The all.
The falling out of that article.
Operative
a piece of cake to. Take
your say Bill I like that I
just take a card off thank you T.J.
. I think it's very nice to
have ladies come there for
a change don't have much of it I thought
is was very popular. To not have to but
would want to drive one of
them I've always want to be
a tightrope walk on the shelf no
you're wrong do that or stick to NOT
a Dr. You don't happen to
know do you wish for them to it was time
to analyse it was it never reached the
lost property office in
the city now there. Was
a matter of fact there was one old fellow
one of us in the trench really means
brother in charge. Now no I'm
wrong there you'll never
find that because you know you're not built
it was no will the Chinaman just didn't
remember the other way because it was
really new so that no he didn't believe we
just did about it trying to kidnap the
people good brand new kind of threw away.
The opening to embarrass the evil will if
he did know me feel bellow in the trap
and shout maze name all around but that
night I said I don't want to run why
a couple right down.
The right.
It was
a good one too all the fuss about just
because the parts market watch shows no
chance got to do it to friends and doesn't
tell me. I was OK Put your hand on the
back.
Yes Governor if you want to find out we'll
watch on him and you're going to lighten
our get not resulting article which is not
far that about thirty miles I want to
get in the militia now you are not
from America which you know. We. Well
you know you have to do non-static
you've got to try. And turn to the left.
Of them by. Many in the news. Tonight.
And I just wish you could.
Get better how you're going to get to
a time when love is hunting or going the
other way on the list of these kind of the
one I'm seeing.
I think it's not with you but you not being
there essentially you know Must you go
on and on about this yes what about you
thought it went to an issue I thought won't
happen with my own kids about tomorrow's
movie want to do I can call on Herman to
my father tried to tell me when I did
this so the conscience is clear if you're
night and you don't stick to
a few minutes then you can be up again but
this may be just what's left for getting
in touch with our wills if
you might be unable to get
a law to help me that doesn't do NOT work
I shouldn't think to or we can do without
if.
I tell him to do it if that's what I love
that's out there to save the country.
How are you is
a long time since we saw you last night and
will be pleased to see you it's nice to
see your name is anteing or is it which
makes the list is birthday oh no she's
having
a party. Who will have her bed not stay
I'd forgotten about the best deal but you
must aim is very good she'd be so
disappointed if you didn't just go ahead the
quite alright.
To which is what. We are about as we
know what what is good is good because
I'm going to tie them together this is
true in this one not two not at all I'm
quite touching on the next thing I do is
the world will not basically impossible to
tell if this is what with this picture
having been pasteurized in the dark but in
a helicopter which might write about it
you know it's just me talking to remember
to this it is best there. Now
children you all know the game
don't get too much of it fun if you have
to go outside and drop headers I once
found that just me to decide
I think I last done. As well
on had all become very good. At
a couple that it's good to know this
came down to I don't think I have
a member on PM I really ought to count the
tourney just come close to the name of
the game used to pay too often enough now
you can watch it if you don't come into
the tent.
This.
Is NEW DAY because just. Because you think
of as early as the heat inside unless
you out there are exhibiting Oh you
should get window issue with this list of
thirty to fifty not a door to
a seven day oh yes Course list is there
to get me he was going there were
a person has missed
a year then you know not to get them
something radically wrong if you've got the
best price but come along you know and I'm
just not not that I can be that you like
to look along the greater sides of.
Erica like there's no status as you bring
a young man the name
outside in the midst of
a few minutes of nonsense to stay
here and see the party go with
a swing. We've seen in some of this party
I'm having an off switch on you will be
so good it's going to time
you. I'm sorry I didn't know
my dad an autistic or did this for
a friend outside I should run people to
look at it and then suddenly I understand
I'm interested if you mean I came across
what you came to be together is that he
didn't. He tells you any
time one of those left
telling pass the guy isn't now and second
as to how he got this inspiring rise you
should be joining
a load. Of the God I
don't. Try doing. Those
things to you having
a nice time and I want. My steps to
come to us not me know what you say I
can just now yes I will present it my
time yet now nonmetallic time now.
Need to come in with if I got it.
To time you. Better get attracted
to you oh it's just Mr though that
Mr. I just did with the
burger and says they're not
exactly quite know this is our jam the I
never remember how many but I suppose you
find that rather difficult in
a not to show metal I'm so sorry I didn't
quite catch your famous name. Of each cup
that include
a village is extraordinary isn't it I
don't ever come across it before they do
actually come along with
a good. Stuff
and I just. Love called that
one so passion after all as
a studio there are any ground in these
things like that to me how it will line up
most. Of the nice little.
It's. Going to be really hard to get
yes I really can be sure this is
a good mind taking is actually for me
or certainly of course are the straw
brilliance is it stalled in the whites
immunised. And I sang then it isn't because
your partner who are.
Disbelieving. Talk Talk of the.
Advertising to make up
a vote is to be uncommon need to keep. It
between learning because I didn't see you
there but just because the system is necessary
to me. There is. Get any clues into
things
a mystery yes often hidden kernel Burgo
unknown Oh yes yes no you'll have to see
this to. My right he said you could just
be talking to us because you want to so
many young men
a status like that work oh I love it I've
heard of it he said it was difficult to
talk to like that the first
half so of course you need
a good deal. I should Potter I would be
much more important yes that's important
certainly but I'm needed so I know because
I mean I can sing his music which he
can't. Until you go by his.
I'll tell you definitely
we're going to. I'm sure
I've got visitors I think I wish you to
go there and I did last night you to come
you have to go so soon as it's an interesting
topic I'll take Mr Manning Cup We
have another game that let's
get the ice except best.
Geoffrey to go well while you are back
to your one grams about Abby's line and
that's for me to decide Harold
Meyerson the first black man
a police this town after town gone I don't
think so Dio do and it was going to me
often very well.
The IT.
It's. Nice to see. You think they're gone
home they are significant but you just
didn't you realize that something going on
between us you didn't know his name
you didn't know him so if you can be
a little gesture it's not the sort. Want
to find out more about them to maybe take
blind man's buff.
They thought it was actually not
going to make another direction.
Team talk and talking. So I
had a mug shot which inevitably
interesting she seemed
a bit suspicious and he said just
naturally you could pitch to test out the
anti-gay under the DI by the producer
trying to do what I want to live in this is
in the garbage she mustn't you. Know he's
very funny and just my name I just said
just the look on your face that we must
not. Say look much better than you love
your wife cause I don't want to make
trouble I feel it's my duty to tell you
anything because how young she is it's an
awkward age because I can understand. It
all this tells me she's going to
live and certainly who she's going.
To go and lean is in and
then I don't like to see
a little bit interaction
I'm sure that she gave
a false name but he didn't get up and it
wasn't him which was in the car when.
It. All right I knew that.
If you never even sent me to Mars it will
be there tomorrow miles and will the
difference between I want them but then I
truly want them to plant because but the
fact that you feel sure the Tampa Bay
people are descending on the doorstep to
spinning down is something Spacey do you
want government to video that why not he's
gone right up to not answer well actually
tell you I hope not if it's up to race
you can bet your heart you can
burst open the door and say with
a sob in my voice if there's
a drop in the boys assist me indicated you
will stand in front of him say I travel
far and risk not you here is the man
in all his innocence to give you
a pep Norma had to say
a little bit odd in his voice tank your
editor thank you for the touches you know
stated
a representative to turn out who had started
to how do you call me Robert. Oh did I
. I didn't it should be to let me know
she didn't make. It you know Maurice.
No I don't remember. If you
have someone with a young man
a pretty. Good attitude when.
You missed the gun. If I just keep comes.
You want you to phone him right away
if you like and the second time.
It was a chap was freaking
a priest got this morning I seen your
picture yet you're becoming so I'm going to
step on it. Really comes and look at
me that we need to. Get out by the
sea because this isn't the boat I was
especially that is to don't think I'm
a Christian except I get to. The
biblical talk about the proper process
to get back up but I can't go back now to
the gym I tried to. I suppose it must be
the man. I just.
Keep my daughter's name not expected. For
the timing of it so right down to one
day he said it is well underway
he probably forced me to go to
a school of thought is the billets Jones
of the ME found there were coming the
funniest news.
It's all right my dealer but it is
a you know this idea printed out in
another company. We can shake hands on
a senior. Attack and uniqueness in.
The context. Of I could tell you there
isn't an. Announcement you know anything.
You know and. You don't believe it's
true. Not always which actually it's.
Just me I like and I was much more
alive in the day. Of those people the
actually eat. I could watch I've got about
one to chill out. Now with the weekly
good fifteen I hand and really
can power request and cost in
a second helping Chan. Well
I'm doing my shopping. And
often doing ten clips of one end
of the next. And I tell you
a lot of. Well now for the lodging house.
But I picture
a woman's heart. With. Well
how do I look.
But I couldn't see. Can't.
Just because. I know I'm going to look.
I could give
a piece. To protect. My
Dad of course. What can I do.
I had to dedicate an honor.
To him today. I'm not. Allowed to own my.
What any. Of it's perfectly
safe I promise. You have
a little nap I'm trying to get on
a bike. And. I
don't want anything. To do.
It In The Big. Wind now
the integers are full.
But
a bit when you left OK then the
six. Where we met Will. Now
have cost is buried. Your parents.
Didn't know he had little.
Or no.
Right.
I don't want any of that business can you
understand I don't want to come here
again I still ride and you keep.
What did they. Get out of the lesson
learned. Here is that your
chin now just will come.
Up.
Which is
a little minute now maybe. That's
the guy music. Is
after all and I'm just back again
very nice and. The Wash may. I'll get
gotten there. I know exactly what you
mentioned and your time your racket in the
air with your childhood and getting
a pair of the back of my china said you
can mend it last time I don't want any
argument from your to last time you come
in here. To me until you just now want to
talk to you and I get you in
a minute it's in my one I gotta talk you've
got something really important to get
a new sister down you'll
never know that was
a mistake so I just think you can
give where was I take you been
a fifty miles too much before
you know anything about
a raincoat. I didn't which you're talking
to that I've got to get into you do know
something about it I'm not interested you
only want to go out on Bill but she's not
the Get tell me you don't expect in
a minute you gotta cook sometimes had to
do to well it's mine only wanted him to
have it afterwards it's no good just in me
I keep tellin ya don't know nothin about
it and while you was
watchin it actually is
a matter of life and death is
going to save me so take me from
a charge of murder of a
preacher after me now by
a comet that's all that I command
that you don't want. To come.
Come on I'm not finished with
you it's what she ought to be
a way to get out of. The place
around. The child and to get.
The frequency off you.
By that way. Yet it happens all
the time if you did not stop.
The atomic bomb if you. Could make them.
Well we've got you.
I didn't know what you were up to Governor
I mean you know I'm saying you know my
pal he's taken me aback not just
talk to doctors shine bright.
I'm too busy. I don't have how than it is
to become busted I want to get home from
here you know. Mine are right.
There. And I'm going to get on the temp
Well you know I would like them out here
where this does not happen to be there was
no bed done he went to bed give it me
and it was my dentist. Who has
a GOOD TO CUT I told you some fellow country
member which you look like yes you big
what I mean pinky caucus. And how he didn't
was because the business budget and you
didn't own outcome it wasn't you. Know
good luck she just has to go through the
piece to never believe
that this would indeed
a mistake to be and as the time said
he was given a practically new as
a coach and I think it's ten times. About
talking more about this appears to catch
up with assume this place to hide what
is Picket's what about three models and
there's
a clot in her life I don't know where
nobody goes much before you get with me oh
what about the old mine workings about
I'm honest I was going to come in
a couple. Just
try don't mind working.
It out but. With the
people I come to me and I'm going
back to configure to. Call on
Miss home and the. Knowledge
that going you know the
chill being involved in this is no fault
of your own. Actually so I thought you
were trying to track him. When he gave you
the slip Why do you think he was making
. I don't know and he said nothing at all
he told Miss Bergeron I'm doing all I can
to make things easy for you will you please
try and make them easy to meet I've got
a job on here and I've got to find
a murdered him I don't show but we're
doing our best you're not comfortable
mistakes are making you find
a pill then follow it to death the evidence
against his will is very strong it's
not going to tell you didn't do it you have
no reason to the government helping me
told you about as he told us
a lot of things we need to talk to some
you might find the religion I should like
to know why you take all this interest in
just because. I have to be in the city he
couldn't tell anything he's much too kind
and gentle why he's the kind of person
I'm sorry to keep you waiting gentlemen.
What's going to back to. Is
a lot to make up to the. Priest
at that time not to do
tonight I didn't hear.
Your father was not to
see you when you can.
Come in and I guess. I wanted us to have
a good talk to get it. I can
quite. And if you didn't want to
speak in front of
a detective. But surely there's something
you want to tell me that might of
this if I was. Your problem is now. I see.
You still desist from shooting a
man wanted for murder. Is not
a matter. You know what I do that
you're committing
a criminal offense. And I responded. With
a reason.
Not to do. It because you stated that.
The of.
The
of.
You. Is if
a team of like the other
such. Men get mixed up with.
This man. I want to push too and.
I didn't. Because I wanted to leave because
the new book At the end of it was.
Presented in the can you supported
a monarchist increase to know those
impossible and now nothing but
a box of matches in the ground.
And got
a little snake. Which you're going. To
want.
Because. It's magic
she granted. Yes but
after the next my life.
There you have
a kitten has been forced
to leave the clan. Well
if it is a Cinderella what.
Were tied to this question up
a level again which means
well that this. And much and
you for the last hour.
I'm so glad you came back I don't know
what headed down the aisle took after that
then you have
a commitment to the good I'm glad
to understand Michael Leach. And
we better start looking for him.
You want to put that. Back down to the
prep they know what that like which is our
goal not. Just military if
you're going to get it done
now and get them recognizing
that. There was
a special never know if he might.
Actually make it yet anyway yes.
Yes the. Table to enter.
Into logic in attempting to get to him
or my children if he is injured and in
particular or. Because I'm the man just to
catch the treaty's in you know times and
tease. And of course.
I. Had it when I learned to live on
a father to get on to see anyone that
attraction to many people might be quite nice
contrast we speak which came
out of our family fiddled with
a question it's an
interesting and some fact. I
think. It was like the palm of my.
Hand and when. We're in
a pair of paper mistakes and I'm right
handed him the old white man like the man
in the brim and then the man the
red and the old. I got to give
a little when I planted the appearance but
when it comes to make them yours and our
thank you bear them all it's an art and I'm
right here to tell you we'll never know
one and like the drama man eh.
Eh.
Eh. Eh.
Eh eh.
Eh. I
feel.
It which is just one of
my. Now well polished.
Everything the pulling the
Senate the Senate one.
Snappy with all these people pregnant that
comical too in the details when we come
to know taken we got to get
a look at some of the pared down
triggers that. Come into now because my
perspective of the government every day
get with the week I'll be off walking
anyway with my old booth in the.
In the a few in
a. One thing with.
A blue one not the only. One
using the lower than
a fool rather than the an old.
One with the nice
a thing you're saying I was
all alone muthafucka got.
A new Congress the war with.
Iran the author.
In the. Life.
And I am thousand.
I want your man. Don't come in again like
that it isn't funny and I pay someone
else to make the orchestrations.
On the phrase no good definitely much good.
It could be what you missed in the Post
quoting now I know I didn't think you'd
notice but it means you might notice
a couple of the looking for Mr Tester.
I shouldn't think and the others on them
I'll take as many as I'd love to write.
And I didn't get in with
a stop this twitch it's got to stop
somewhere it's getting on my net. As.
I want to thank you for your patience nothing
generation moving beyond is going to
sell his ability to help his cause going
to hit you whatever you can fix nothing
you know that I was doing that
nothing you needed to have
a small item of humanity if you didn't
think of that soon it might have saved
a great deal of trouble for the human side
I don't plan to get this guy any other
man.
Without. Asking about.
In.
The school.
In the. In.
I'll.
Get back in their right place
where the. Registers and.
What happens I can't wait am I
going to start trying to find
a doctor that is keeping the what to do on.
A company so your last episode of stage
was much of
a success really controversial
mantra once it. To
let me. Get to campus that's
a. Little while.
The side. I'm on my subject.
The TO MISS IT people right.
You guys and it was ten percent
compared to. What did you do with the
don't the country. What did I do.
The puppy. I push to get round her
neck and trip the life out of the rock
I kept up the pop pop pop pop and I.
Wanted me to write it to try. It.
Out and. Then to think you
can you can do this in.
The air.